


import '../../../models/language_four_model.dart';

late List<WordFindQues> listQuestions = [
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "đấtnước",
    // shuffled: "cấntưđớ",
    hintindex:3,
    count: "7",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "điệnảnh",
    // shuffled: "nảniệđh",
    hintindex:4,
    count: "7",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "cúsốc",
    // shuffled: "súccố",
    hintindex:2,
    count: "5",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "concua",
    // shuffled: "accoun",
    hintindex:3,
    count: "6",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "ốcvít",
    // shuffled: "cíốtv",
    hintindex:2,
    count: "5",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "lybia",
    // shuffled: "bylai",
    hintindex:2,
    count: "5",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "baphải",
    // shuffled: "apbiảh",
    hintindex:2,
    count: "6",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "đắcchí",
    // shuffled: "cắchíđ",
    hintindex:3,
    count: "6",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "tríkhôn",
    // shuffled: "kíhtônr",
    hintindex:3,
    count: "7",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "dạikhờ",
    // shuffled: "kờdhại",
    hintindex:3,
    count: "6",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "hoànhã",
    // shuffled: "oãhhàn",
    hintindex:4,
    count: "6",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "trăngnon",
    // shuffled: "ngonăntr",
    hintindex:5,
    count: "8",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "bốcđồng",
    // shuffled: "gđồcbốn",
    hintindex:3,
    count: "7",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "hạnhphúc",
    // shuffled: "cạnhhúph",
    hintindex:3,
    count: "8",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "cốcđá",
    // shuffled: "cđcáố",
    hintindex:3,
    count: "5",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "độclập",
    // shuffled: "ậpộđcl",
    hintindex:3,
    count: "6",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "thanhtịnh",
    // shuffled: "hanịtthhn",
    hintindex:3,
    count: "9",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "tronglành",
    // shuffled: "loànghtrn",
    hintindex:5,
    count: "9",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "thiênnhiên",
    // shuffled: "niêthênihn",
    hintindex:5,
    count: "10",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "câycối",
    // shuffled: "ốcâcyi",
    hintindex:3,
    count: "6",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "quốctịch",
    // shuffled: "huốcqịtc",
    hintindex:4,
    count: "8",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "khảnăng",
    // shuffled: "nảngkhă",
    hintindex:4,
    count: "7",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "khoahọc",
    // shuffled: "ọachhko",
    hintindex:4,
    count: "7",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "lòngđất",
    // shuffled: "gấnđòlt",
    hintindex:4,
    count: "7",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "phânbón",
    // shuffled: "hópbânn",
    hintindex:4,
    count: "7",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "hoangmang",
    // shuffled: "ganhomnga",
    hintindex:5,
    count: "9",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "thếgiới",
    // shuffled: "hitiếgớ",
    hintindex:3,
    count: "7",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "đồnghồ",
    // shuffled: "gồđồnh",
    hintindex:4,
    count: "6",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "nonsông",
    // shuffled: "songônn",
    hintindex:3,
    count: "7",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "nôngnghiệp",
    // shuffled: "hôgninệpng",
    hintindex:4,
    count: "10",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "giaothông",
    // shuffled: "taogingôh",
    hintindex:4,
    count: "9",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "samạc",
    // shuffled: "camạs",
    hintindex:2,
    count: "5",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "hoangdã",
    // shuffled: "gãnaodh",
    hintindex:4,
    count: "7",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "hònđảo",
    // shuffled: "nođòhả",
    hintindex:3,
    count: "6",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "vẻđẹp",
    // shuffled: "đẻpvẹ",
    hintindex:2,
    count: "5",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "độngvật",
    // shuffled: "gậntộđv",
    hintindex:4,
    count: "7",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "thanhniên",
    // shuffled: "nanênihth",
    hintindex:5,
    count: "9",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "búagỗ",
    // shuffled: "agúỗb",
    hintindex:3,
    count: "5",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "biệtthự",
    // shuffled: "hệttbiự",
    hintindex:4,
    count: "7",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "tuổitrẻ",
    // shuffled: "rutẻitổ",
    hintindex:5,
    count: "7",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "giáoviên",
    hintindex: 4,
    count: "8",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "xãhội",
    hintindex: 2,
    count: "5",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "chínhsách",
    hintindex: 5,
    count: "8",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "thịtrường",
    hintindex: 3,
    count: "9",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "diđộng",
    hintindex: 2,
    count: "7",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "giáoán",
    hintindex: 4,
    count: "6",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "phòngthủ",
    hintindex: 5,
    count: "8",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "thịthực",
    hintindex: 3,
    count: "7",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "camkết",
    hintindex: 3,
    count: "7",
  ),
  WordFindQues(
    question: "Hãy sắp xếp những từ sau thành từ có nghĩa",
    answer: "tínhiệu",
    hintindex: 4,
    count: "7",
  ),
];
